Yes, this is our short video of the 30 series and the
five videos we have made before this are
very informative,
what happens for constipation for beautiful health insurance,
how to click, so if you want to understand then
you can refer to those videos also,
in this video we are going to talk about something
which generally people do not know, if people have a
health insurance policy then
it does not claim the goods
which is their amount and the
insurance company gets the benefit of it, so
in this video we are going to talk about which is that
money which you unknowingly leave,
which you do not clear
and then the reason is that you do not read the comments on this, due to which
you do not know
that this money which is your money,
which you should take only for yourself, so
whenever you are admitted in the hospital for cashless
hospitalization,
you have also taken reimbursement and
if this claim is approved by your insurance company, then
after that you become liable for
free hospitalization
expenses and post hospitalization
space, pre and post hospital
What does this mean? These days are defined in your policy.
Generally, 30 days before i.e.
Jupiter reaction and seven days after
i.e. all the post hospitalization
expenses are borne by the insurance company. But
your policy document is often
closed in maximum policies. If
not in your policy, then issue a different or similar
policy in which it is closed. So what
happens in this is that suppose
you were admitted in the hospital on 1st date of this month,
your treatment was done and you
went home after taking the benefit of the insurance, then
consider it as the entire 30 days from 1st date of the previous month. If
you were admitted on 1st June, then the
expenses of the entire 30 days of May, whether you spent on your medicines
and chaat, paid the doctor's fees,
tea, you had some chilli samsar, the
insurance company will give you the money for this. In the same
way, if you are discharged from the hospital, then
Malwa will be discharged on Muktipath June.
Then whatever expenses you have for the next year's Ayan
from 5th June to 5th August, whatever
your expenses will be on medicines, doctor's fees, whatever you have done, that will be borne by
you.  The
insurance company will pay you the
money under the full and post hospitalization
coverage.
For this, when your claim is finalized and completed,
you need a claim settlement letter for your post hospitalization.
After that, you have to fill the form and along with that
claim form, you have to send all
your invoices of all your expenses, both the
day before and seven days
after, to your insurance company along with
your bank details. Then the
insurance company processes it and
transfers the money you spent (including any expenses other than hospitalization) to you.
One thing to keep in mind is that whenever you are
sending a claim for reimbursement, keep
a copy of the claim with you
because it often happens that the
documents get misplaced and then it becomes
difficult for you to get the claim. In that case,
you can re-claim the claim from the copy you have, you
can go to the insurance company.  Since you had submitted this,
I hope you liked this information
and if you really liked the information then
share it with as many people as possible and if you have come to the channel for the
first time then subscribe to the channel and
also press the bell icon button so that
you keep getting such informative videos first and on
time and
you should also watch my upcoming videos on help body so
that you do
not have to spend anything extra from your pocket while getting admitted to the hospital
and you should do only as much as is necessary.
Thank you.